Prasenjit Kumar Nag (Joy)

2/24 Adelaide St, St Albans, VIC 3021, Australia

□ (+61) 416-690-697 | ■ joyruet06@gmail.com | ♠ joycse06.github.io | ☑ joycse06 | ♦ joycse06 | ≧ prasenjit-kumar-nag | 🛅 prasenjitnag

"Be the best you can be."

Summary

Current Senior Technical Lead at Bellroy. 9+ years experience specializing in backend development. Super tech-savvy who loves Vim, NixOs and OSX and enjoys working on all layer of the stack. Nurtures growth mindset, believes in deliberate practice and takes every challenge as a learning opportunity. Experienced in converting complext ideas/business requirements into functional solutions using the right tools (even if they are outside of confort zone).

Skills

Back-end Ruby On Rails, Resque/Sidekiq, Dry-rb, Redis, Memcached, PostgreSQL, Laravel, REST API

Front-end Elm, React, Redux, HTML5, SASS, Webpacker

DevOps AWS, Docker, Kubernetes, Vagrant, CloudFormation, Terraform, AWS CodeBuild, CodePipeline, EMR, Athena, Redshift, Aurora,

Programming Ruby, PHP, Haskell, ReactNative, SQL, Bash Script **Programming** Ruby, PHP, Haskell, ReactNative, SQL, Bash Script

OSes OSX, NixOs, Ubuntu, Debian

Languages Bengali, English

Experience

Bellroy (TrikeApps was merged into Bellroy)

Melbourne, Australia

SENIOR TECHNICAL LEAD Nov. 2017 - Present

 Provisioned an easily managable hybrid infrastructure (Amazon AWS + On-premise) utilizing IaC (Infrastructure as Code) tools like Ansible, Packer and Terraform.

TrikeAppsMelbourne, Australia

TEAM LEAD

Apr. 2017 - Oct. 2017

 Provisioned an easily managable hybrid infrastructure (Amazon AWS + On-premise) utilizing IaC (Infrastructure as Code) tools like Ansible, Packer and Terraform.

TrikeApps Melbourne, Australia

RUBY DEVELOPER

Apr. 2016 - Apr. 2017

 Provisioned an easily managable hybrid infrastructure (Amazon AWS + On-premise) utilizing IaC (Infrastructure as Code) tools like Ansible, Packer and Terraform.

Astute Payroll Melbourne, Australia Melbourne

PHP SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Feb. 2016 - Mar. 2017

 Provisioned an easily managable hybrid infrastructure (Amazon AWS + On-premise) utilizing IaC (Infrastructure as Code) tools like Ansible, Packer and Terraform.

Adgate Media Remote

WEB DEVELOPER

Feb. 2015 - Jan. 2016

• Provisioned an easily managable hybrid infrastructure (Amazon AWS + On-premise) utilizing IaC (Infrastructure as Code) tools like Ansible, Packer and Terraform.

Noobis Inc Dhaka, Bangladesh

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Jul. 2011 - Sep. 2015

• Provisioned an easily managable hybrid infrastructure (Amazon AWS + On-premise) utilizing IaC (Infrastructure as Code) tools like Ansible, Packer and Terraform.

Allmoxy Inc Remote Part Time

WEB DEVELOPER

July. 2012 - May. 2013

 Provisioned an easily managable hybrid infrastructure (Amazon AWS + On-premise) utilizing IaC (Infrastructure as Code) tools like Ansible, Packer and Terraform.

Remote Part Time

Web Developer Intern

Dec. 2009 - Jun. 2011

• Provisioned an easily managable hybrid infrastructure (Amazon AWS + On-premise) utilizing IaC (Infrastructure as Code) tools like Ansible, Packer and Terraform.

TrikeAppsMelbourne, Australia

RUBY DEVELOPER

April. 2016 - April. 2017

• Provisioned an easily managable hybrid infrastructure (Amazon AWS + On-premise) utilizing IaC (Infrastructure as Code) tools like Ansible, Packer and Terraform.

Education.

Rajshahi University Of Engineering And Technology

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Feb 2007 - Aug 2011